Oleksandr Romaniuk



oleksandr.romaniuk.work@gmail.com



380964915706



linkedin.com/in/oleksandr-romaniuk-613005143



https://oleksandrdev.com/

Summary

Most of my work experience is as freelancer at Upwork.

There I work on list of projects with tasks like add new functionality, resolve issues etc.

Back-end development (Python/Django/Flask/DRF/DjangoCMS/WagtailCMS)

Experience with deploy Django apps (AWS EC2, Apache/Nginx, PostgreSQL or Docker/Docker Compose).

Working with PostgreSQL, Docker, Docker Compose, Git, AWS EC2/S3

Experience



Freelance Web Developer

none

Feb 2020 - Present (1 year 10 months +)

M Approver

Mindy Support
Dec 2017 - Feb 2020 (2 years 3 months)

Education



LNTU

Master's degree, Commodity science and trade entrepreneurship 2015 - 2020

Skills

Python • Django • Flask • Docker • Web Development • Bootstrap • PostgreSQL • DRF • Docker Products